孩子们 故事发生在巴尼的生活
Kids, this is the story of the night
完完全全的分崩离析的那天晚上
Barney's life completely fell apart.
我的生活终于完美了
My life is finally perfect,
六小时前
而且再也不会变了
and that is never going to change.
准备好今晚跟我妈妈吃饭了吗
Fired up for dinner with my mom tonight?
这样吧 为了让我们今后的生活更有效率
Yeah. To help streamline the rest of our lives,
你可以一直默认我对这个问题的答案是否定的
you can always assume my answer to that question is no.
-这...  -我就是挺紧张的
-W... -I'm pretty nervous.
紧张 有什么好紧张的 不就是两个小时的
Nervous? Why? It's just gonna be two hours
"我最爱巴尼了" "不 我才最爱巴尼呢"
of "I love Barney the most." "No, I love Barney the most."
你说的没错 那我可能连话都插不上
You're right. I may not even get a chance to talk.
但我还是...
But I'm still...
我不知道 我只是担心
I-I don't know. I'm worried
她会觉得我没那么好
she won't think I'm good enough to be engaged
配不上跟她的小可爱订婚
to her precious little Love-Love.
好吧 首先 应该是"小口耐"
Okay, first of all, it's "Wuv-Wuv."
其次
And second,
就放一百个心吧
don't worry.
我先去把婚宴承办人的定金交了
I'm just gonna drop off our catering deposit,
然后就来陪你 亲一下
and then I will be there for you. Mm.
好吧 千万别来晚了
Okay, well, please don't be late.
今晚我就指望你了
I am counting on you tonight.
还有小心点 那里面可是五千块钱呢
And be careful-- that's 5,000 bucks in there.
我觉得我在上东区就走上四个街区
Uh, I think I'll be okay walking four blocks here
是完全没有问题的
on the Upper East Side.
求你们了 我发誓我没跟北朝鲜人说过话
Please, I swear I never talked to the North Koreans!
除非你们就是北朝鲜人 这样的话
Unless you are the North Koreans, in which case
我就从来没跟南朝鲜的人说过话
I never talked to the South Koreans!
巴尼•斯丁森
Barney Stinson,
你被绑架了
you are being kidnapped.
绑你去惊喜单身派对
For your surprise bachelor party!
老爸\N　　　  　　 老妈\N　　 　　 浪漫史\N　　  　　　　第八季  第二十二集\N
S08E22 The Bro Mitzvah
翻译: @Mr_Gao703 @rubink2011 @纷扬DLL\N@卟哒哒伽马 @麟礡 @阿狸小H\N校对: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花
压制: @Big-Fudge\N统筹+后期: @我叫肉鸭鸭 @晒小花
HIMYM字幕组 倾情奉献
绑架是吧
A kidnapping.
不错不错
Respect.
我私下里还担心
I was secretly worried
你们俩搞定不了我的单身派对呢
you might not be able to pull off my bachelor party.
少来 哪有私底下
Yeah, it wasn't that secret.
就你们俩 计划我的单身派对
You two? Planning my bachelor party?
三周前
听着 你们真是乖娃娃
Look, you seem like nice kids.
但这是件庄严神圣的大事
But this is a sacred event,
一个男人跟他的兄弟们一起度过的仪式
a man's rite of passage with his bros.
他的...兄弟受诫礼
His... bro mitzvah!
这才不是你刚灵机一动想出来的
You didn't just think of that.
你这几个月就一直在念叨...
You've been saying it for months every...
但我也有我的难处
But here's my dilemma:
平常人的单身派对 对我来说也就是平常的夜生活
my average night is like an average guy's bachelor party.
所以 无意冒犯 但是如果你俩来计划
So, no offense, but if you two plan it,
这也就会是 平...凭什么要等一下..了个常
it's gonna be ordi-- why wait for it?-- nary.
平常
Ordinary.
我可以帮忙
I can help.
就你
You?
听好 你看起来也算蛮会倒腾的
Look, you seem like a nice kid,
但是兄弟的未婚妻
but bros' fiancées
不能参与计划单身派对
cannot plan bachelor parties.
不好意思 你俩自己搞定
Sorry. You two are on your own.
你们一定会让我失望的
And you will disappoint me.
但尽量弄好点 行吧
But make it great, okay?
这个开头很带劲啊
But this is a strong start.
这些学生们 已然成为
The students have become...
中级学生了
the intermediate students.
我先打个电话
I just have to make one call.
喂
Hello.
罗宾 好消息
Robin, great news!
我被绑去参加一个惊喜单身派对去了
I've been kidnapped for a surprise bachelor party
所以我来不了了
so I won't be there at all!
什么 巴尼 我做不到就我一人陪你妈妈吃饭啊
What? Barney, I-I can't do dinner with your mom alone.
好吧 我给她打个电话 找个借口把它取消了
Okay, I'll call her, make up an excuse and cancel.
别担心 有事我全扛着
And don't worry, I'll take all the blame.
等会
Hold on.
嗨 小口耐
Hi, Wuv-Wuv.
嗨 麻麻
Hi, Momsies.
我都忘了 我今晚要给一个失学儿童补课呢
I forgot, I'm mentoring an underprivileged child tonight,
罗宾又受不了就她一个人陪你吃饭
and Robin can't stand the idea of dinner with you by herself,
所以我们就不能...
so we're not gonna be able to...
不用麻烦了 她都已经到了
Don't bother. She's already here.
等会
Hold on.
罗宾 太晚了 她已经到了
Robin? Too late. She's already there.
巴尼 别...
Barney, don't...
罗宾受不了一个人陪我吃饭吗
Robin can't stand the idea of dinner with me?
太好了 那我们都说好了
Great! We're all set then.
别让我一个人陪她 我跟你说过...
Don't you leave me alone with her. I told you...
问题解决
That problem is solved.
现在你们什么计划
So what's the plan?
好吧 你知道大西洋城的泰姬陵赌场吗
Well, you know the Taj Mahal in Atlantic City?
知道
Yeah.
你知道大西洋城的泰姬陵赌场的楼顶
You know the secret penthouse
有一套秘密豪华套房吗
in the top of the Taj Mahal in Atlantic City?
知道
Yeah!
看呐 就在那儿
Boom! There it is.
从我们的窗户可以看见
Visible from our window.
就是有点距离
In the distance.
在炼油厂后面
Behind the refinery.
好吧 基本上看不见
Okay, you can't quite see it.
为什么我们就偏偏在大西洋城外围啊
Why are we outside Atlantic City?
呃 我们觉得这样才能不负恩泽
Well, we thought it was best,
因为你玩机会博弈那类游戏真真是极弱的
what with your weakness for games of chance.
孩子们 巴尼痴迷于
Kids, Barney was addicted
一种中国的赌博游戏
to one Chinese gambling game
这个游戏在S02E08出现过
那游戏 呃 有点复杂
that was, well, sort of complicated.
不过别担心
But don't worry.
你早在和昆茵订婚那会儿
Back when you were engaged to Quinn,
就告诉过我们你今晚想要什么了
you told us everything you wanted for tonight.
单身派对是一个男人的
A bachelor party is a man's...
十个月前
兄弟受诫礼
bro mitzvah!
你刚瞎掰出来的吗
Did you just think of that?
正是如此 我们可以戴上
Totally! We can wear...
黑色小哥帽
bro-mulkes...
转个兄贵小陀螺
spin the bro-del...
还要聆听伟大的兄弟卷轴中的智慧
and consult the wisdom of the Bro-rah.
用希哥来文写的
Written in... He-bro.
哥们真是一点也不冒犯呢
Not at all bro-ffensive.
对了对了 还有些别的主意呢 我就全一股脑写上去了
Ooh, ooh! Couple other ideas-- and I'm just spitballing here--
爱要要 不要拉倒
so take 'em or leave 'em.
美酒 不用说 雪茄 少不了 脱衣舞娘 必须有
Booze, duh; cigars, duh; strippers, duh...
对了 既然我们迟早会玩过头
Ooh! Things should get so crazy that at some point
某种程度上我们还该敬畏生命
we should fear for our lives.
我们一定会敬畏生命的
Oh, we'll fear for our lives, all right.
那就一起来看艾尔•戈尔的《难以忽视的真相》吧
When we watch Al Gore's An Inconvenient Truth!
好啊 我们可以玩每听到一次
Yeah. We're gonna pound a beer
"灾难性"这个词 就吹掉一瓶啤酒的游戏呢
every time we hear the word "Catastrophic"
哦
Oh!
会不会是
Could that be...
你清单上的下一条项目呢
the next item on your list?
爽翻天的视听盛宴
Mind-blowing entertainment,
比如裸体火舞或者裸体魔术之类的
like a naked fire show or a naked magic show.
我们的婚约很有可能
There's a good chance our engagement
会告吹 不是吗
doesn't work out, isn't there?
双关 "暂时不会"
不谈这个啊 亲爱的
Not now, honey.
又或者是裸体柔术
Or a naked contortionist!
或者是 气球柔术
Or... A balloon contortionist!
气球
Balloons.
不是我今晚想看见的那种
Not the inflatable, round, squishy pouches
充气的 圆圆的 黏糊糊的小气球
I was hoping to see tonight.
等一下
Hold on.
我跟你说了不要叫小丑
I told you no clown.
但你也不喜欢那个吹泡泡的啊
Well, you didn't like the bubble guy either.
好啊 罗宾
Hey, Robin.
你是不是跟你妈妈说
Did you tell your mother
我是处女啊
I'm a virgin?
什么 你为什么会这么想
What? Why would you think that?
留着点肚子吃甜点
Save yourself room for dessert. Mmm.
据说你在自我保留方面极其突出呢
And I hear you excel at saving yourself.
你太逗了
You are so funny.
是不是什么东西上身了
What's gotten into you?
哦 没错 从来没有过
Oh, that's right, nothing ever.
你可能会对
You may be nervous
新婚夜将要发生的事情感到很紧张
as to what goes where on your wedding night.
很简单的
It's really simple.
我给你演示一下
Let me show you.
我们从最基本的姿势开始学吧
Let's start with the fundamentals.
你为什么告诉她我是处女
Why would you tell her I'm a virgin?
我慌了嘛
I panicked.
就是 我真心希望她会喜欢你
Look, I really want her to like you,
就忍受一下吧 好吗 好的
so just go with it, okay? Okay!
听着 小口耐 你最好立刻马上滚回...
Listen, Wuv-Wuv, you better get your ass back...
又有人来了呀
Another guest?
会是谁呢
Who could this be?
哇 是莉莉
Why, it's Lily!
她是来满足
And she's here to deliver
你的一个要求的
one of your requests!
哦 谢谢 马修
Oh, thank you, Marshall.
哦 不是这个要求
Oh, not that one.
见到我一直以来的偶像
An appearance by my all-time idol,
龙威小子
the Karate Kid!
《龙威小子》是80年代一部振奋人心的经典电影
The Karate Kid was an uplifting '80s classic
讲的是拉尔夫•马奇奥扮演的一个少年的故事
about a teen, played by Ralph Macchio,
他打败了威廉•扎布卡饰演的地头蛇
who defeats the local jerk, played by William Zabka.
至少大部分人是这么认为的
At least, that's how most people saw it.
他来了 还是和以前一样帅
Here he is, just as hot
正如同当年他的《老虎队》杂志照给了一个年轻姑娘
as when his Tiger Beat photo spread gave a young girl
十足的勇气去探索
the courage to explore
自己那突然变得凹凸有致的身体
the suddenly unfamiliar topography of her changing body...
龙威小子
the Karate Kid!
嘿 巴尼 我是拉尔夫
Hey, Barney. It's Ralph.
一直以来 我十分荣幸...
Listen, it's always flattering...
不
No!
我讨厌拉尔夫•马奇奥
I hate Ralph Macchio!
我讨厌他 讨厌他 讨厌他
I hate him, hate him, hate him!
他才不是什么龙威小子
He is not the Karate Kid!
威廉•扎布卡才是龙威小子
The Karate Kid was William Zabka,
眼镜蛇道馆的明星学员
star pupil of the Cobra Kai Dojo,
这头禽兽
who this monster
用一记卑鄙的 违规的高踢腿击败了他
defeated with a cheap, illegal head-kick
成就了电影史上最让人怨念的悲剧结局
in the most tragically haunting film ending of all time.
哦 懂了 我还以为你说他是有趣的那种疯子呢
Oh, see, I thought you meant fun-crazy.
闭嘴 拉尔夫•马奇奥
Shut it, Ralph Macchio.
你干嘛不去找卢克•天行者
Why don't you go have a party with Luke Skywalker
哈利•波特还有战马之类的其他电影大反派们开派对
and Harry Potter and War Horse and all the other movie bad guys
巴尼对电影正反派总有自己独到的认知
别来毁我的派对
and stop ruining mine!
真是灾难性的一晚
This night has been catastrophic.
灾难性 大家吹瓶
"Catastrophic"! Everybody pound.
对不起 兄弟
Sorry, bro.
我留下了
I'm staying.
如果这
If this is anything
像我的单身派对一样 脱衣舞娘 美酒
like my bachelor party-- strippers, booze,
绝对不做手活儿 你懂的
definitely no hand stuff-- wink-wink--
这将会变得不可...等一下...思议
it is gonna be in-- wait for it-- credible.
不可思议
Incredible!
哇
Wow.
你们俩还真是挺像的
You guys are actually a lot alike.
你最好把话收回去 先生
You take that back, sir!
我一点都不像拉尔夫•马奇奥
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!
我说 你们到底有没有去请脱衣舞娘啊
I mean, did you guys even get a stripper?
兄弟
Bro.
我们当然请脱衣舞娘了
Of course we got a stripper.
我们难道看起来像那种傻到
Do we look like the kind of dweebs
连脱衣舞娘都不请的傻帽吗
who wouldn't get a stripper?
就像谚语里说的一样
And as the saying goes,
在大西洋城外面的平价商务旅馆
what happens in the sensibly-priced
里发生的事情就留在
business hotel outside Atlantic City stays
大西洋城外面的平价商务旅馆里
in the sensibly-priced business hotel outside Atlantic City.
改编自 在维加斯发生的一切就留在维加斯里
是谁
Who is it?
警察 我们接到了一个噪声扰民举报...
Police. We got a noise complaint from...
噢 我在骗谁呢 这里都死气沉沉的
Oh, who am I kidding? I can tell it's dead in there.
我是脱衣舞娘
I'm the stripper!
巴尼
Barney?
昆茵
Quinn?
这是你的单身派对吗 你又订婚了吗
This is your bachelor party? You're engaged again,
我们分手还不到一年啊
less than a year after we broke up?
是和罗宾吗
Is it Robin?
等会儿
Now, hold on.
你不是唯一的一个有这么多问题想问的
You're not the only one with questions here.
你们连脱衣舞娘的底细都不摸清吗
You didn't vet the stripper?!
好吧 看到你幸福我很开心
Well, I'm glad you're so happy.
我们分手以后 我不得不搬出纽约
After we broke up, I had to move out of the city,
我的车也被毁掉了 我只好重操旧业
my car got totaled, and I had to go back
继续当脱衣舞娘来付房租
to stripping just to pay rent.
举目四望 我的人生都已经无路可走了
It's like everywhere I look, my life is a dead-end.
哇
Wow.
我很...我很抱歉 昆茵
I am... I'm so sorry, Quinn.
那 你想怎么样
So, how does this work?
是给我私人演出呢 还是其他人也...
Do you give me a private show, or does everyone...?
我不会为你跳脱衣舞的
I am not stripping for you.
你们保证我会有咪咪看的
I was promised boobs.
噢 拉尔夫 如果你想的话 我可以...
Oh, Ralph, if you want, I can...
莉莉
Lily.
那是龙威小子吗
Is that the Karate Kid?
是 是 是
Yes! Yes! Yes!
不是
No!
他还真挺像巴尼的 是吧
He's a lot like Barney, huh?
你最好把这话收回去 女士
You take that back, madam.
我一点都不像拉尔夫•马奇奥
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!
好 好
Okay, okay.
这样吧
I'll tell you what.
我要为在场的每一个人表演脱衣舞
I am going to strip for everyone here
巴尼除外
except Barney.
我会跳的相当淫荡的
And I'm gonna make it dirty.
搞清楚状况 我是单身派对的主角
Yeah, um, I'm the bachelor.
新郎的首席大腿怎么能不在场呢
Kind of no stripping without the lap of honor.
帮我说几句啊 兄弟们
Back me up, bros.
嘿 罗宾
Hey, Robin.
嘿 亲爱的 在你的单身派对上玩得开心吗
Hey, sweetie, having fun at your bachelor party?
-不开心  -太好了 我在这里简直是生不如死
-No. -Good, 'cause my night's been hell!
这就是倒扫烟囱式
And that's the inverted chimney sweep,
十七种基本爱爱姿势的最后一种
the last of the 17 basic sexual positions.
现在 捆绑...
Now, bondage...
停 我根本不是处女
Stop! I'm not a virgin!
我的餐巾环已经接待过无数的面包条了
My napkin ring has seen plenty of breadsticks.
还有一根法式长棍面包
And one baguette.
我和尼克斯队的一个中锋约会过
I dated a center for the Knicks.
谢天谢地你不是老处女
Oh, thank God you're not a prude.
我们终于可以说人话了
Now we can really talk.
来四杯科斯莫葡萄酒 快点
Four cosmos, pronto!
现在她喝醉了
Now she's drunk,
正抓着一个餐巾环和三个面包棍
holding up a napkin ring and three breadsticks,
大谈特谈她大战克罗斯比 斯蒂尔和纳什的那一夜
and talking about her night with Crosby, Stills and Nash.
克罗斯比 斯蒂尔和纳什是一个乐队
服务员 可以给我再来一条面包吗
Waiter, can I have another breadstick?
还有杨
And Young.
乐队全称是Crosby, Stills and Nash (and Young)
你回来好吗
Please come back.
好
Okay.
我很快就到
I'll be there soon.
相当漂亮 非常美妙
Real nice. So beautiful.
我觉得我们做到啦 我们真的做到啦 是吧
I think we really did it. I think we did it, you know?
你啥也没错过哈
You didn't miss a thing.
-噢 昆茵  -怎么啦
-Oh, Quinn? -Yeah?
你那里沾了...一点东西
You got a little... something.
噢 哦
Oh! Oh.
咱们调头回去吧
Let's head back, guys.
这一晚上从头到尾都是低能
This night has been completely half-assed.
你显然错过了脱衣舞表演
You obviously missed the strip show.
泰德 这可是我的单身派对
Ted, this was my bachelor party.
一个人一生中就那么两三次
A man only gets two or three of these in his lifetime.
你就是这么对我的吗
And this is all you do for me?
够了 就此结束吧
That's it, I'm calling it.
谁需要搭便车回纽约
Who needs a ride back to the city?
噢
Oh.
噢 大伙儿 等下 先等下
Oh, guys, wait, hold on, hold on.
喝酒
Drinking.
一口闷
A shot.
射击
Shooting.
枪
A gun.
枪击
Shot, gun.
你要副驾驶位吗
Shotgun?
天 真是挤死了
Man, it's crowded in here.
没错 就跟坐在小丑车里面似的
I know, it's like a clown car.
小丑的车子通常很小很拥挤
如果我磨在拉尔夫的大腿上 倒是可以腾出些地方
Well, I can make some room by grinding on Ralph's lap.
坐在
sitting!
我 我是说 坐在
I-I meant, I meant sitting.
这简直是史上最烂的单身派对
This is the worst bachelor party ever.
哦 我的单身派对简直是天...等一下...
Man, my bachelor party was incr-- wait for it--
你们最好是饿了
and I hope you're hungry,
因为这个词的后一半是...菜啊
'cause the second half of this word is-- edible!
天才啊
Incredible!
自我握手
Self-shake.
你快把你说的咽回去 小丑
You take that back, clown.
我跟拉尔夫•马奇奥完全是两派
I am nothing like Ralph Macchio!
没错
Yeah.
你和小丑的共同点还多些呢
You've got more in common with the clown,
只不过他那套衣服比你的贵些
except his suit's more expensive.
嘿呦
Hey, yo!
我是说 哪个怂货会在
I mean, what kind of loser
离亚特拉大城不远的地方办单身派对
has his bachelor party ten yards from A.C.
却没去赌一把
and doesn't even gamble?
哦 不好意思
Oh. Oh, sorry.
对不起啊 不是故意的啊
Sorry. Sorry.
不好意思
Sorry.
哦 等一下
Oh... oh, wait.
再来一小下
Just a little more.
好啦 对不起啦
Okay, sorry.
好啦
Okay.
金龙翻来 哩个系
兄弟受诫礼
bro mitzvah!
孩子们 赌博的细节就不详细说了
Kids, I'll skip over the gambling.
跟我之前提到过的一样 这规则十分繁琐
Like I said, it was a complicated game.
不过你们老爹倒是很快就搞懂规则了
Although your old man did pick it up pretty quickly.
嘿
Hey!
你一下就赢了300刀啊
You just won 300 bucks!
我一下就输了5000刀
I just lost $5,000.
哦 对 因为是只鸡
Oh, right. 'Cause the chicken.
没错 这样就是5000刀
Yep, that-that's $5,000, yeah.
你看 我笑是因为
See, I'm laughing
你没能领略我脱去上装的风采
because you couldn't see me take my top off,
-我却能目睹你把衬衣都输掉了的惨样  -嘿呦
-but I just saw you lose your shirt. -Hey-yo!
咱该回去了
We have to go back.
怂货 对不起 刚才真的打了个喷嚏
Loser! Sorry, that was a real sneeze.
你们怕是没听清我刚说什么吧
Might have made you miss what I was saying.
怂货
Loser!
我们哪都不去了
We're not going anywhere.
我还有机会力挽狂澜让今晚变成传奇
I can still make this night legendary.
啊 啊
Uh, uh...
哦哦
Oh, oh.
好 我赊到钱了
Okay, I got some credit.
我只需要 呃
I just... mm...
马修 站那边去给我些好运
Marshall, stand over there for good luck?
哦 没问题
Oh, sure.
好的 好的
Okay, okay.
一
二
三
四
哦 哦
Oh! Oh!
你这个狗娘养的 你成功啦
You crazy son of a bitch, you did it!
我刚输了八万刀
I just lost $80,000.
哦 对对 没错 因为那个黑色软糖
Oh, right, right, yeah. 'Cause the black jelly bean.
那就是八万刀 他说的没错
That-That's $80,000. He's right.
告诉你哦 拉尔夫
You know, Ralph,
之前我去了沙龙 身上涂满蜜蜡 然后统统都刮掉了
Earlier at the salon,I waxed on,then waxed off
一丝不剩
Everywhere.
呃 听着 女士 你的老公就在...
Uh, listen, lady, your husband is, like...
嘿 你老公哪去了
Hey, where is your husband?
马修
Marshall?
马修哪去了
Where's Marshall?!
好吧 莉莉 别反应过激哦 其实呢
Okay, Lily, don't overreact, but...
你有乜嘢俾我
我可以信任你 但是你要给我个抵押品
好啦 他们又赊了点给我
Okay, I got some credit.
马修 站那边去给我些好运
Marshall, stand over there for good luck?
哦 没问题
Oh, sure.
给金龙八万块的筹码
你把我老公卖掉了吗
You sold my husband?!
莉莉 你能不能多学学中国黑帮
Lily, can you be more like the Chinese mobster
给我也放个高利贷啊
and give me some credit?
我会去赎马修回来的 只是需要弄些钱
I'm going back for Marshall; I just need to get some money.
完全用不着担心 他们是"好的"黑帮
You have nothing to worry about; these are the "Good" Mobsters.
哇哦 什么样的跳梁小丑会这样对待朋友
Wow, what kind of bozo does that to a friend?
bozo也有混蛋的意思 通常用来骂白人
闭嘴 拉尔夫•马奇奥
Shut it, Ralph Macchio!
不 你才闭嘴
No, you shut it!
拉尔夫•马奇奥说的没错 你就是个跳梁小丑
Ralph Macchio's right, you are a bozo.
呃 我觉得他们的意思是"浅色人种"
Um, I think they prefer "People of bright color."
昆茵也是金发白人
你知道单身派对的意义何在吗
You know what a bachelor party's about?
就在于和你的朋友在一起玩的尽兴
Hanging out with your friends and having a good time.
但是只在乎自己尽兴 把朋友放一边去了
But you only care about the good time, not the friends.
所以说你给我听好了
So you know what?
我也不再关心你了
I'm-I'm done caring about you then.
我走了
I'm out of here.
泰德
Ted...
泰德 泰德 我刚...
Ted, Ted, I have...
我刚刚好不容易摆脱掉 你那尼克•诺尔特的正面照
I just tore your mom away from a living version
活物版的老娘 然后叫了辆车送他回家
of a Nick Nolte mug shot and put her in a cab home.
"尼克•诺尔特的正面照"美国明星烂醉被捕照片 形容烂醉如泥
我谢谢你在我
Thank you for abandoning me
人生中最糟糕的夜晚 抛弃了我
on what has been one of the worst nights of my life.
好的 你知道我的价码 不过我会因为
So, it's my usual fee, plus I always charge
小丑蹭酥胸的环节多要一百刀
an extra hundred for girl-on-clown action.
她在这干什么呢
What the hell is she doing here?
罗宾 我发誓 什么都没发生
Robin, I swear, nothing happened.
意思就是只有手活
That means just handstuff
-你  -嗷
-You...! -Oh!
不 住手 别打了
No, no, stop, stop, stop!
对不起 巴尼
Sorry, Barney,
这事 这件事我没法原谅你
this... this-this is unforgivable.
我们结束了
It's over.
其实
You know...
我一直没机会这样做
I never got to do that.
泰德吗
Ted?
我是罗宾
Robin.
一切按计划进行
We're right on schedule.
-巴尼都想死了算了呢  -我知道 这太棒了
-Barney is suicidal. -I know, it's awesome!
是的 孩子们 我们计划好了
Yep, kids, we had planned out
那天晚上的每一个步骤
every step of the night.
这一切都从三周前开始说起
It started three weeks earlier.
你们一定会让我失望的
...and you will disappoint me.
但尽量弄好点 行吧
But make it great, okay?
哦 一定会很棒的 放心吧
Oh, it'll be great, all right!
经过整整两周的苦思冥想
Okay, after two weeks of brainstorming,
目前我就想到了普瑞来
all I have on my list so far is Purell.
普瑞来 洗手液公司
马修 你呢
Marshall, what do you got?
多亏你 现在没了
Well, nothing now.
这根本不可能完成啊
This is impossible!
你要怎么给一个将人生每个夜晚都安排的有声有色的人
How do you make something memorable for a guy
设计另一个另人难忘的夜晚呢
who makes every night the best night of his life?
给他最糟糕的夜晚就行了
Give him the worst night of his life.
我们订个最差的房间
We'll give him the worst hotel room
招数之"巴尼"
安排最烂的节目
with the worst entertainment,
错的龙威小子
the wrong Karate Kid,
还有他最不想见到的脱衣舞女
and the absolute last stripper he would want to see.
等等
Hold on.
你希望我装作生活一团糟
You want me to pretend my life's gone to crap
不得不重操旧业 只是为了整蛊前未婚夫吗
and I'm back to stripping just screw with my ex-fiance?
这我喜欢
I love it!
派对太糟糕 差到他急着想离开
That party will be so terrible, he'll have to leave it.
然后我会让他狡猾的宿敌说...
Then I'll instruct his arch-nemesis to say...
什么样的怂货才会在
what kind of loser has his bachelor party
离亚特拉大城不远的地方办单身派对 却不去赌一把
ten yards from A.C. And doesn't even gamble?
巴尼会拿着我给他的一信封现金
Barney will take the envelope of cash I gave him
掉头直奔我们的陷阱
and head straight into our trap.
等等
Hold on.
你希望我们在赌局中出老千
You want us to rig a casino game
来整蛊一名以前挥土如金的高级常客吗
to trick one of our former high rollers?
呃
Um...
我爱这个计划
I love it.
恩 那到时候你就让
Well, then you get Barney
巴尼选他们中的一个作为抵押
to use one of these guys as collateral.
-他应该会选我  -什么
-He'll probably choose me. -What?
是啊 我更值钱
Well, I'd be worth more.
有一口好牙
Yeah. Perfect teeth.
是哈 只是
Yeah, it's just, uh,
只是我的运动神经比你好多了
just I'm way more athletic than you.
是哈 这句话是从一个
Yeah, this coming from the guy
滑雪球从没赢过我的人嘴里说出来的
who's never beaten me at skee-ball.
人家黑道爷会选择你的唯一理由是
The only reason a mobster might choose you is because
他们怕遭到我"被解救的马修"的报复
they'd be afraid I'd go all "Marshall Unchained" On them,
而明显你就构不成什么威胁
which obviously isn't a risk with you.
是吗 你想看看"被解救的泰德"吗 啊
Oh, you want to see some "Ted Unchained," Huh?
我就让你看看"被解救的泰德"
I'll show you Ted Unchained!
马修 你能不能
Marshall, would you mind
站到那边去 给我点好运
standing over there for good luck?
哦 当然可以
Oh, yeah, sure.
与此同时 我会确保
Meanwhile, I'll make sure
他会在我最噩梦的场景中 放我鸽子
he's abandoned me in my nightmare scenario.
等等 你希望我帮你整自己的儿子吗
Hold on. You want me to help you trick my own son?
我爱这个计划
I love it.
巴尼活该
Barney deserves it.
你知不知道 他告诉我你是处女
You know, he told me you were a virgin.
太荒谬了
Ridiculous!
我也觉得
I know.
你是个荡妇 跟我一样的
You are a dirty ho-bag just like me.
可他却这么地爱你
But he loves you so much.
我也好爱你哦
And so do I.
等等 这些事情对巴尼
Wait, hold on. Is there any chance
会不会有点太过分了
this is all too mean to Barney?
开个玩笑
Just kidding.
好了 现在只需要完成最终乐章了
Okay, we just need the finale.
哦 中国黑帮把我的手咔嚓砍下来
Oh! The Chinese mobsters chop off my hand
让巴尼亲眼目睹
right in front of Barney!
就是这样 我们全都一样兴奋
Yes, we're all equally enthused!
好了 计划是这样 在我甩手走人之后...
Okay, here's the plan. After I storm off...
巴尼
Barney!
巴尼 快点 把钱给他们
Barney, hurry! Give them the money!
-求你了 快点啊  -哦 不好
-Please, hurry! -Oh, no!
中国黑帮要把马修送回来
The Chinese mobster is giving Marshall back
换我去当人质
and taking me hostage instead,
因为他说明显是我更值钱
because he says I'm obviously more valuable!
你能 能把门打开吗
Can you, can you unlock the door?
巴尼 求你了
Barney, please!
不然他们就要砍掉我的手
They're gonna chop off my hand!
他们不会的
No, they're not!
他们说了你自由了 而且我记得
They said you're free, and I think
我们都同意这不是黑道爷会做的事
we agreed that's not something mobsters would do.
泰德 别闹了 这是我的戏份
Ted, come on! This is my thing!
别伤害他
Don't hurt him.
我有钱
I've got the money.
太迟了
Too late!
别砍我玩滑雪球这只手啊
Not my skee-ball hand!
-不  -不
-No...! -No...!
不要
No!
求你们 别射我的脸 或者裆部
Please, just don't shoot me in the face... or the crotch!
惊喜吧
Surprise!
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
是这样 我们决定帮你
Well, we decided to give you
完成你在单身派对上想做的每一件事情
everything you wanted for your bachelor party
而且让你毫不知情
without you even realizing it.
等等 这就是你让我以为马修可能会死的原因吗
Wait, so that's why you made me think Marshall might die?
还让我以为我输光了所有钱 我的朋友们都讨厌我
And I'd lost all that money and my friends hated me
我的婚礼也取消了 是吗
and my wedding was off?
你就决定用所能想象到的
You just decided to-to check off
最极端最扭曲的方式来完成单子上的每一项吗
everything on this list in the most twisted way imaginable?
真真是太赞了
That is awesome!
而且这全是某个女孩一手策划的哦
And it was all planned by a girl.
哇哦
Wow!
那 莉莉...
So, Lily...
一会儿你想不想 呃...
later on tonight, you want to, um...?
喔 喔 喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
刚才那只是演戏的一部分
That was all just part of the act.
你是知道的 对吧
Y-You knew that, right?
知道啊 当然知道
Yeah! Totally.
咱们圆满完成了 不是吗
We pulled it off, right?
柏拉图式握手
Platonic shake!
大家听我说 感谢你们为我办这么棒的兄弟受诫礼
Everyone, everyone, thank you for an incredible bro mitzvah.
恭喜兄弟
Mazel brov!
原为Mazel tov 希伯来语里恭喜的意思
恭喜兄弟
Mazel brov!
嗯 你其实没有把单子上的每一项都做完
Mm, oh, you didn't really get everything on the list.
无意冒犯啊 拉尔夫•马奇奥
N-No offense to Ralph Macchio,
但他才不是龙威小子呢
but he ain't the Karate Kid.
我完全同意你的说法
I couldn't agree with you more.
你知道 他们差点就不能请到我了
You know, they almost didn't get me.
但在18个语音留言之后
But after 18 voice mails...
我回了罗宾的电话
I returned Robin's call.
她告诉我
And she told me
你是这世界上少数几个
how you're one of the few people in the world
真正理解《龙威小子》这部电影的人之一
who truly gets The Karate Kid movie.
所以当她问我能不能帮忙时
So when she asked if I'd help,
我的答案只可能是...
well, my answer just had to be...
是
はい
威廉•扎布卡
William Zabka!
HIMYM字幕组 谢谢观看
欢迎关注字幕组新浪微博及人人网主页
@HIMYM字幕组